apparelmagic.com 2015-10-06

# ApparelMagic – Apparel Software, Cloud, PLM, ERP, Accounting – Privacy Policy

Your Privacy is very important to us and we want you to know how we respect and protect your privacy.  The security of personal Information about you is our priority. We protect your information by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that meet applicable law.  We train our employees in the proper handling of personal information. When we use other companies to provide services for us, we require them to protect the confidentiality of personal information they receive.  
If you disagree with our existing Privacy policies currently or as may be modified in the future, we will provide opt out options to protect you.  Your secure information, such as Passwords are never stored as plain text and are encrypted for your protection.  You should be careful to maintain the secrecy of your passwords and/or account information and be responsible about protecting your personal information and identity whenever you are online.

We do not sell your personal information to third parties for any reason. We do not disclose your information to unaffiliated third parties, or to our affiliates, who may want to offer you their own products and services unless you have requested or authorized us to do so.  We may share your information with third parties where it is necessary for us to complete a transaction you authorized or perform some other activity you have asked us to do.  
We may share your information with third parties or affiliates with whom we have contracted to perform services on our behalf. All companies that act on our behalf are contractually obligated to keep the personal information we provide to them confidential and to use the personal information we share only to provide the services we ask them to perform.  
Our Services, including sites, may contain links to third party sites. Please be aware, however, that we are not responsible for and cannot control the privacy policies of these other sites or their practices. We encourage you to read the privacy policies for these other sites, as they may differ from ours. This Privacy Policy applies solely to personal information collected by us.  
Except as described in this statement, information you provide will not be transferred to third parties without your consent. We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as packaging, sending, and delivering promotional materials and other mailings, answering customer questions about software or services, processing event registration, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.  
ApparelMagic may access or disclose information about you in order to: (a) comply with the law or respond to lawful requests or legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of ApparelMagic or our customers, including the enforcement of our agreements or policies governing your use of the services; or (c) act on a good faith belief that such access or disclosure is necessary to protect the personal safety of ApparelMagic employees, customers or the public.  
If ApparelMagic should  merge with another company, or purchase another business, or sell or reorganize part of its business, it may be required to disclose your personal information to prospective or actual purchasers and other parties. It is our practice to obtain appropriate protections for information disclosed but we cannot, however, guarantee that our Privacy Policy will remain unchanged in this event.  
EMAIL PRIVACY:  
Why did you receive a mailing from us?  
Our email marketing is compliant with CAN-SPAM laws in the USA. If you received a mailing from us, our records indicate that (a) you have expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future (“opt-in”), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with one of our marketing partners. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.  
If you believe you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, or have any questions about our policies, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to info@apparelmagic.com for review.  
How can you stop receiving email from us?  
Most marketing emails we send contain an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the links at the bottom of the email.  Or contact us at info@apparelmagic.com.  
How we protect your privacy:  
We use appropriate security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.  
Sharing and Usage  
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone for their promotional use without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law.  Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information.  
Use of Web Beacons  
When we send you emails, we may include a web beacon to allow us to determine the number of people who open our emails. When you click on a link in an email, we may record this individual response to allow us to customize our offerings to you. Web beacons collect only limited information, such as a cookie identifier, time and date of a page being viewed, and a description of the page on which the Web Beacon resides (the URL).  
Web Beacons can be refused when delivered via email. If you do not wish to receive Web Beacons via email, you will need to disable HTML images or refuse HTML (select Text only) emails via your email software.  
From time to time, we may change this policy.  If you disagree with our existing Privacy policies currently or as may be modified in the future, we will provide opt out options to protect you. The effective date of this policy indicates the last time this policy was revised or materially changed.  Checking the effective date allows you to determine whether there have been changes since the last time you reviewed the policy.
